export const QuestionsJson = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s favorite N64 game and character of choice",
      "answerText": "Game: Mario Kart, Character: Yoshi",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 200,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "questionText": "What would Trey say is Angela’s favorite currently existing bar on Broadway",
      "answerText": "Bootleggers",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 200,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s favorite Bloomer family memory",
      "answerText": "Trips to Myrtle Beach with his family as a kid",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 200,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "questionText": "What would Trey say is the one thing that Angela does that annoys him the most",
      "answerText": "Can't sit down and relax at home",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 200,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "questionText": "What would Trey say is Angela's most embarrassing moment together",
      "answerText": "Her puking and passing out in the car in Los Angeles on our way to LAX after a wedding",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 200,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "questionText": "What  is Trey's weirdest quirk",
      "answerText": "Nervous tick where he run my hands in his hair real fast",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 200,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s favorite non-N64 game to play with Angela? Card, lawn, board, tv, etc.",
      "answerText": "Skip-Bo, but Anglea always wins",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 400,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s favorite brewery in town",
      "answerText": "Bearded Iris",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 400,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s favorite story he’s heard about a Cox family memory",
      "answerText": "The story about how David and Lucia wouldn't give Angela a dog but instead gave her some birds and then they ended up with million birds after they mated",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 400,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "questionText": "What would Trey say is the one thing he does that annoys Angela the most",
      "answerText": "Doesn't clean the gerbil cage on time",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 400,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "questionText": "What is Trey's favorite sex position",
      "answerText": "Her on top",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 400,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "questionText": "What is the first thing Trey noticed about Angela on their first date",
      "answerText": "Her boobs! Sorry babe!",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 400,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "questionText": "What YouTube music video is Trey most likely to play on tv",
      "answerText": "Destiny's Child: Say My Name (for Angela, of course!)",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 600,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s favorite festival or event in town",
      "answerText": "CMA Fest with Angela",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 600,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "questionText": "If Trey could live in any country (besides USA) where would he live",
      "answerText": "Spain",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 600,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "questionText": "What is Trey's biggest pet peeve in general and what would Trey say is Angela's biggest pet peeve in general",
      "answerText": "Trey: People asking him to repeat himself because they weren't listening, Angela: People not following through on what they say they will do",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 600,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "questionText": "What is Trey's favorite trip he has taken with Angela",
      "answerText": "Portland, Maine",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 600,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "questionText": "What song puts Trey in the mood *AND* would Trey say puts Angela in the mood",
      "answerText": "I'll Make Love to You by Boyz II Men, but then we both laugh because it's so cheesy",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 600,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "questionText": "What games has Trey taught Angela",
      "answerText": "Trick question, Angela has played every single card/board game. She teaches them all to him!",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 800,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s go to drink recipe",
      "answerText": "Beer, but whiskey and ginger ale otherwise",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 800,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "questionText": "If Trey had to name your first child RIGHT NOW what first and middle name would he choose",
      "answerText": "Oh God, I have no clue. Boy: James Trey | Girl: Elizabeth Lucia ????",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 800,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "questionText": "What TV show/movie does Trey hate watching with Angela",
      "answerText": "Teen Mom and all Real Housewives",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 800,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "questionText": "What would Trey say is the funniest memory he has of the two of you together",
      "answerText": "After dinner and drinks with Chris and Jackie in Cincinnati, Angela and I took Remy out to use the restroom. We starting walking across this cobblestone/brick pathway and Angela says watch your step because I had just rolled my ankle pretty badly the week before. The moment she says that, I say 'I'm good!' and immediately twist my ankle again! Wasn't funny in the moment but is now. Ankle swole up to the size of a softball.",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 800,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "questionText": "Name one room in your house Trey says you have NOT had sex in",
      "answerText": "The front dining room",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 800,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "questionText": "As of August 7th, what was Trey’s current Skipbo score on the wall",
      "answerText": "12",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 1000,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "questionText": "What is Trey’s favorite drink that Angela has introduced him to",
      "answerText": "cabernet sauvignon",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 1000,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "questionText": "What amount of money would Trey accept to hyphenate your family’s name to Cox-Bloomer",
      "answerText": "$10 million",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 1000,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "questionText": "How many times would Trey say that ‘sexy time’ has been somehow interrupted by Remy and/or Tanner",
      "answerText": "Oh, not that many. Like a handful, 4-5 times. We can usually ignore them",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 1000,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "questionText": "What is Trey's favorite memory of the two of you together",
      "answerText": "Proposing to her on top of Craggy Garden Summit in Asheville",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 1000,
      "clicked": false
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "questionText": "Who was Trey's first real kiss with",
      "answerText": "Megan Moore in 10th grade",
      "showQuestion": false,
      "value": 1000,
      "clicked": false
    }
  ]
}
